{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120845424","data":{"timestamp":" 947120845423"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120854512","data":{"timestamp":" 947120854512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120854734","data":{"timestamp":" 947120854734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120855697","data":{"timestamp":" 947120855697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120856971","data":{"timestamp":" 947120856970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120859832","data":{"timestamp":" 947120859832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120860674","data":{"timestamp":" 947120860674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120860987","data":{"timestamp":" 947120860987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120862221","data":{"timestamp":" 947120862220"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120865741","data":{"timestamp":" 947120865741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120866725","data":{"timestamp":" 947120866725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120866978","data":{"timestamp":" 947120866978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120867921","data":{"timestamp":" 947120867921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120870769","data":{"timestamp":" 947120870769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120871802","data":{"timestamp":" 947120871802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120872274","data":{"timestamp":" 947120872274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120876799","data":{"timestamp":" 947120876799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120876874","data":{"timestamp":" 947120876874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 8110743c-66a7-4208-b4ec-91fbeeec0b5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120887127","data":{"timestamp":" 947120887126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 0fd20cd9-d52b-4c16-8078-415008fb9b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120888459","data":{"timestamp":" 947120888459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 0fd20cd9-d52b-4c16-8078-415008fb9b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120888528","data":{"timestamp":" 947120888528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" 0fd20cd9-d52b-4c16-8078-415008fb9b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120898608","data":{"timestamp":" 947120898608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" a9eb73ee-fcf7-4e32-99d6-ea661c59d960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120916139","data":{"timestamp":" 947120916139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" a9eb73ee-fcf7-4e32-99d6-ea661c59d960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120920385","data":{"timestamp":" 947120920385"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" a9eb73ee-fcf7-4e32-99d6-ea661c59d960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-4-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120925773","data":{"timestamp":" 947120925773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" a9eb73ee-fcf7-4e32-99d6-ea661c59d960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-2-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120931619","data":{"timestamp":" 947120931619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" a9eb73ee-fcf7-4e32-99d6-ea661c59d960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947120943698","data":{"timestamp":" 947120943698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_040650"," gameId":" a9eb73ee-fcf7-4e32-99d6-ea661c59d960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}